Characters, actions, locations, occupations and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
(Any activity that I can do on my own—)
(I believe it’s what God created for me.)
(And even if He didn’t,
I could still handle it myself.)
(I became a photographer)
(because I thought I wouldn’t
have to talk to too many people,)
(and I’d get to see people
from different perspectives every day.)
Have you decided?
Do you have anything cheaper than this?
Do you want a film camera?
That’s only 300 baht.
A disposable one.
What kind of photography do you like?
Here.
You can borrow mine.
If we run into each other at a studio
someday, just give it back then.
(But I guess I was wrong,)
(because when people call you
one of the top in the country,)
(this job is never peaceful again.)
Please put the perfumes away, and separate
the color-graded from the ungraded ones.
Peach!
(She’s probably the only chaos I allow
and love having in my life.)
(My sister, Plub.)
Without Plub’s connection,
I couldn’t have booked a top photographer
in the country for this project.
I’m not that good, Nuch.
You’re that good.
I emailed and called, but couldn’t
get in touch with you, Mr. Peach.
Meanwhile, Plub kept her lips sealed
and wouldn’t tell me she’s your sister.
You just don’t have what it takes.
Couldn’t help you there.
No need to call me Mr.,
and you probably reached out
during my break.
I’m sorry.
No worries.
My brother is a free-spirited freelancer.
He only takes jobs when he feels like it.
Thank you so much for feeling like
taking this one, Peach.
Without you, I’d be in trouble.
Mr. Aran specifically requested to work
with a photographer he’s close to.
That’s you, Peach.
Great. That’s great.
That’s great too.
Awesome, Ran. Can you change the pose?
Give me a side glance.
One. Two.
Three. Four.
Okay, Ran.
This time, I want you
to spray the perfume.
Portray the scent.
Follow the timing.
One. Two. Three.
Okay.
Alright, three shots.
This set should be good to go.
Can we switch the reflector
for the softbox?
Thank you.
I think all of these look good.
-Is it okay?
-Yes.
How’s it going?
Do I look handsome today?
Don’t you trust my skills?
Come see for yourself.
I know you can make me
look handsome no matter what.
I brought the shots for you to approve,
Mr. Top Model.
Great.
Aren’t you going to answer the phone?
I don’t want to talk to him.
I’m tired of the same old stuff.
If you don’t like Tawan,
why not just tell him?
This is wasting both of your time.
I don’t want to talk about this anymore.
Let’s change the topic.
Are you going to the wrap party tonight?
No, I’d rather stay home and sleep.
Come on.
You know I don’t like
these kinds of parties.
Besides, I’m just a freelancer.
I’m not close with anyone.
You’re close with me.
It’s different.
The wrap party is one thing.
But don’t you want to be there
for Arseni’s new ambassador launch?
Here, look.
The new brand ambassador is ready
to spark a next-level sensation.
Wow.
I’ll go change.
Okay.
Theerakit Kian Lee.
The most unforgivable thing is a mistake.
That’s the new perfume
from the Spring Collection.
The butler must have grabbed the one
the team prepared for you to try by mistake.
I’m sorry.
You can leave.
The Fall Collection party tonight
starts at 8.
According to the schedule,
you’ll have to give a speech.
You know I don’t do things like that, Mok.
Don’t pretend you don’t know
why I’m going to the party tonight,
even though it disgusts me
and drives me insane
to be around crowds
who are only after my power.
They said Mr. Aran
is already at the event.
Now that’s what I want to hear.
I’m going to the restroom.
Don’t sneak off.
Can I get another glass, Note?
You got it.
Watch him. Don’t let him leave.
Leave it to me.
Cool.
I’ll be right back.
Note.
Yes?
Where’s Plub?
Something came up at work,
so she couldn’t come.
Hey.
It’s okay.
I’ll take care of you tonight.
Come on. Cheers.
Have a little.
Awesome.
Beautiful.
Hey!
So what?
Peach!
Ran.
What are you doing there?
You’re always like this when you’re drunk.
Sorry about my brother.
He’s always like this when he’s drunk.
I’m sorry.
Please excuse us.
Shall I get him in the car?
No, I’m not in the mood anymore tonight.
But—
I’ll let him have his moment for now.
Don’t think you can get away from me,
my little lemur.
What just happened?
Tell me. What do those people want?
I don’t know.
They handed me a 10-million check
out of nowhere.
10 million?
My boss wants to sleep with you tonight.
Why the hell would you say that?
Where’s your boss?
Hey! You must watch too many soap operas
if you think you can throw your money
at everyone like they’re nothing.
Is the money not enough?
Do you want a blank check
to fill in the amount later?
Hey!
What are you doing?
So what?
Too bad I didn’t get to tell them off.
They pushed me down first.
Tell them off?
Ran!
Didn’t you see they had guns?
Yes.
But only when I was about
to punch their boss in the face.
It’s okay.
Hey!
Peach!
What are you doing, Tawan?
So you didn’t answer my calls
because you were with this photographer?
Are you okay, Peach?
I’m fine.
Peach saved me.
Saved you? I saw you were going to hug!
Have some sense, Tawan!
We’re not even anything yet.
If you’re just going to be hotheaded
and refuse to listen,
then leave!
But if you want to get a grip and talk,
go wait by the car.
Otherwise,...
we don’t have to see each other again.
Okay.
I’ll wait by the car.
I really apologize on Tawan’s behalf,
even though I’ve done it
countless times before.
I’m really sorry.
Ran, are you okay?
I don’t know.
But if there comes a day
when I’m not okay anymore,
you have to drink with me.
Of course.
I’m envious of Plub for having you
as an older brother.
You’re basically my little brother.
Is your hand okay?
It’s nothing.
Just go sort out your situation.
See you.
It’s bleeding?
You can’t open it with your hand
hurting like that.
Thank you.
That’s what happens when you
stick your nose where it doesn’t belong.
If it hurts, just cry.
Why are you pretending to be strong?
It doesn’t make me
want to admire you more.
Well, it doesn’t hurt.
Why would I cry?
What do you think you’re doing?
My breath will ease the pain
you’re going through.
He watches too many soap operas.
If I got bitten by a snake,
he’d probably try to suck the venom out.
I'm...
I’m sorry for stopping you
in the restroom,
but that’s my little brother,
and it’s clear he wasn’t willing.
Please let Ran go.
You should know that someone like me
always gets what I want.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I was just shocked to hear you say that.
What do you mean?
I didn’t think anyone would
actually say that in real life.
It’s bossy and self-centered.
Are you scolding me?
Watch yourself.
I could totally crush you.
Did that model tell you
how much more money he wanted?
Hey, get a grip.
You can’t buy Aran with money.
You probably can’t imagine
how much money I have.
I’ll have you know, my money
can buy everything in this world.
Have we met somewhere?
Why do you look so familiar?
Please step back.
Your way of seducing is really bad.
Did you learn that from soap operas?
Theerakit Kian Lee.
You’re the owner of Arseni.
Now, do you want to call that model
to come running back to me?
Being the brand owner is all the more
reason you shouldn’t be doing this.
Aran is your brand ambassador.
You should show him some respect,
not act like this.
You’re lecturing me.
Well, I should go.
Since you’ve started, keep going.
Lecture me to your heart’s content.
I…um…
I’m already content.
Please excuse me.
Damn, what the hell?
Sucking snake venom out with your mouth
only happens in cheesy dramas.
Everything he says sounds weird.
Hey.
Oh, hey, Peach.
I thought Note said work came up.
Why are you home?
The promotion team was rushing
to get the materials,
so I had to choose the photos and
plan the graphics guidelines for them.
Are the photos okay? Any issues?
Not at all.
If I’d known the work was this neat,
I’d have gone to the party with you.
I barely had to do anything
for each photo.
Just adding some text,
and it’s good to go.
But I’ve been waiting for you
because something else came up.
What is it?
Please become Arseni’s
regular photographer, Peach.
Everyone loves your work.
They asked me to beg you.
Please.
Arseni?
Can you sit properly?
You’re an adult now.
Alright, Dad.
Thank you.
Come on.
Hey.
Why did you mention my company earlier?
Are you interested in becoming
our regular photographer now?
Have you met the owner of your company?
The owner?
You mean Mr. Thee?
Whenever he comes,
he goes straight to the top floor.
He rarely visits other floors.
Unless you’re someone
high up on his floor,
you usually don’t get to see him.
Why do you ask?
Well, I met him at the party.
Did you two talk?
That’s for the best.
People say just being near him
sends shivers down their spine.
You’d better stay away from him.
Someone got told off and ran crying
from his room to HR.
She quit right away.
Is it that bad?
Yes.
Rumor has it that his perfume business
is just a front for money laundering.
Arseni’s real business is shady.
They have a network overseas.
I’m here as Arseni, not anyone’s son.
Not anyone’s proxy.
Then act like it.
Didn’t your father tell you?
I’m not here to buy your stupid perfumes.
And they also say that
some days, Mr. Thee’s sleeves
are stained with blood.
What?
(I’ll go.)
(Don't think you’ve won.)
(All this time,)
(it’s my fault for not seeing the truth.)
(What do you see now?)
-(Now, I only see you.)
-Now, I only see you.
You’re the one I’ll love
forever.
THE END
Yes, Boss?
Tell the station to keep rerunning
Shadow of Vengeful Love.
Keep it in the primetime slot.
Yes, Boss.
Is the other thing I asked for
taken care of?
This is his full background file.
What’s that?
Mr. Peachayarat’s profile.
I prepared it just in case.
But if you don’t—
Why is there so little information
about his family?
Mr. Peachayarat only has
one younger sister.
Her name is Panachakorn.
She’s a full-time employee on
Arseni’s graphics team.
Make a restaurant reservation for me.
Pick somewhere that will make
a good first impression on him.
But Mr. Aran is shooting all day today.
I’m afraid—
Did I accidentally say Aran’s name?
Please leave the parcel
in front of the house.
You’re in trouble, Peach.
I’ll just pretend to be asleep.
(They say anyone who offends Mr. Thee
either goes missing)
(or ends up getting killed.)
No.
No! No!
No!
Hello.
How many minutes
do you need to get dressed?
Get dressed?
Mr. Thee wants to have lunch with you.
Huh?
I’m giving you 15 minutes.
Mr. Thee has already started the timer.
THEE 1, BANGKOK
Please get in the car.
Which one?
Hello.
Wait, is there still space
in the car behind?
I shouldn’t have asked.
Why are you so tense?
Where’s the audacity from last night?
I was probably a bit too drunk last night.
I’m sorry if I did anything bad.
I didn’t tell you off, did I?
What did I say that made you think that?
Why don’t you talk
like you did last night?
I’m speechless.
You’re scared of me?
A little.
Just a little?
A little more.
Not just a little.
Order as much as you want.
Pardon?
Boss said you can order anything
you’d like, Mr. Peachayarat.
Oh, I can eat anything.
Please order whatever you want.
But I want to know
why you brought me here today.
Huh?
Boss just sighed. He hasn’t said anything.
Please excuse me.
Please continue.
Your way of seducing
hasn’t improved at all, Peachayarat.
I moved this close to you because
I couldn’t hear you from far away.
Please stop thinking
I’m trying to lock you down.
That’s ridiculous.
Ran is your type. I’m nothing like him.
You’ll never fall for me.
If this is a challenge to earn pity,
you’d score at least 99 out of 100.
Why did you bring me here?
If you’re going to kill me, I beg you,
please don’t.
I have a younger sister to take care of.
Boss saw that you’re close with Mr. Aran,
so he wants more information.
That’s it?
I hope I’ll hear some good advice
from your smart mouth, Peach.
Let’s break up.
I understand.
Ever since I started dating you,
I’ve gotten so much better at being alone.
Let’s go our separate ways.
I see you as my best friend.
I just got broken up with
for being too boring.
I don’t think I’m the right person
to give you advice, Mr. Thee.
So you’re single now?
Aren’t you going to eat with us?
There’s plenty of food.
Mr. Thee, you’re serious about Ran, right?
What do you mean?
I’ll help if you’re serious about him,
I mean, if you want to date him.
But if you just want sex,
I have to be honest,
I’m not okay with that.
My brother is not that kind of person.
How do I make a move on him?
Maybe you could start with a gift.
How about a car?
Are you crazy?
The first thing you’d buy
to build a connection is a car?
He won’t like it, huh?
A diamond ring, then.
Come on.
Get a grip, Mr. Thee.
That’s too expensive.
How is a car expensive?
Just a small bouquet will do.
That can be an apology for yesterday, too.
A bouquet?
Small.
I repeat, small.
As encouragement for a workday morning.
I think that’ll be enough
to make Ran happy.
And you?
What would make you happy?
Me?
Why are you asking about me?
Wait.
I took up your time today.
How much money do you want?
Would 10,000 be enough?
What?
Is that not enough?
Why are you giving me money?
You did well, and I’m satisfied.
It’s only right that I reward you.
You throw money around like this
all the time, huh?
You might not think my money
is a big deal,
but it solves everything.
If I didn’t know a bit about you,
I’d be really mad at what you just said.
Actually, I’m a bit mad.
Your words are confusing me again.
You talk like you’re throwing money at me.
What you said was really mean, you know?
How is repaying you for your kindness mean?
Treating me to a meal today
is more than enough.
I’m leaving.
I don’t let anyone walk away from me
when I’m not done talking.
Then just say what you have to say.
Does that little meal
really mean that much to you?
That little meal cost like 10,000.
I’d never spend that much
of my own money on it.
Yes, it’s really delicious and I’ve been
wanting to try this place for so long,
but it’s not worth you spending that much
just to get advice about Ran.
You’re the one losing out here,
and you still want to pay me?
What are you rambling about?
I don’t understand.
If you don’t know how to repay people when
they make you feel good or impress you,
just saying thank you is enough.
I’m heading out.
Thank you for today.
Thank…
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
(You’re welcome.)
Hey.
Mr. Thee!
Do we have any shoots
at the studio tomorrow?
Yes, we’re shooting a video ad.
A video ad?
Mr. Aran will model for us as usual,
and we got a skilled camera operator,
but it’s not Mr. Peachayarat.
Mmm.
But Mr. Peachayarat is coming in
to take behind-the-scenes photos as usual.
Next time, just say everything at once.
Why hold back?
I’m sorry.
Order a small bouquet for Aran.
What kind of flowers would you like?
Anything.
It’s up to you.
Got it.
Is that all, Boss?
Wait.
And you?
What would make you happy?
Why are you asking me?
I’m just asking for a reference.
I don’t think you can use me
as a reference for this.
Just answer me. Is that so hard?
Chocolate, I guess.
The more bitter, the better.
Order chocolate for Peach.
Yes, Boss.
Make sure it’s not sweet.
The more bitter, the better.
Get the most expensive brand
and prepare a card too.
What should I write?
I’ll write it myself.
I’ll write, “Take care of it.”
(If you come a little closer,)
(you'll hear my heart beating your name.)
What kind of heart beats a person’s name?
Right, Boss?
That’s his idea of a small bouquet?
Hey, Peach.
I didn’t know you were coming.
I came to get the behind-the-scenes
photos for the magazines.
You’re all set.
Thank you.
I just found out that the mafia boss is
Mr. Thee, who owns Arseni.
I almost punched my own boss.
What are you going to do
now that you know he’s your boss?
If he doesn’t interfere with my work,
I’m fine.
But if he tries to force me
to sleep with him to get work,
I’d rather quit.
I knew you’d think that way.
He sent you a bouquet, though.
Maybe it’s to apologize for that night.
I actually don’t hold it against him.
Rich kids are all spoiled.
I’ve met plenty of them.
Be right back. I’m going to the restroom.
Okay.
Hey, there you are.
There’s a delivery for you.
This?
Yes, this one.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Hmm?
“Take care of it.”
TAKE CARE OF IT. - THEE
Take care of what?
Who is this for?
It must be for Aran.
Chocolate?
Who bought this for me?
The one who sent you the bouquet.
Mr. Thee again?
Take it. I don’t want to eat it.
-It’ll make me fat.
-What?
Have some, Ran. He bought it for you.
I’ll take a bite, then.
Ugh, it’s so bitter.
Just how you like it.
Try it.
Alright.
It’s not bitter at all.
It’s good.
It’s premium-grade chocolate.
Then I guess he bought it for you.
Why would he buy it for me?
Hey, Ran.
In 15 minutes, please change
and get ready for the next shoot.
Okay.
See you soon.
See you.
Take it, Peach.
It’s yours. He bought it for you.
You said it’s good, right?
You can have it.
Just take it.
You’re unbelievable.
Get back to work.
I’m going then.
Yeah, I’ll follow you in a bit.
Great lighting, shots, and composition.
Everything is perfect,
including the model.
Mr. Ran, please just go with the vibe.
You’re feeling refreshed,
there’s a gentle breeze,
and you’re enjoying it.
Okay.
That’s professional.
Don’t blow too hard or his hair will fly.
Just blow softly.
Great job.
Hey, Peach.
Look, he just randomly came down
to watch us work.
The AC in this studio
was already freezing.
Now it’s getting even colder.
I don’t think it’s anything.
What? Nothing?
Look at my director.
He’s shaking like crazy.
I’ll get him something to drink.
He needs warm water.
Oh, no!
Mr. Thee.
I bought you that chocolate,
but you fed it to someone else.
Uh…that was for me?
You’re insane!
You can’t even figure that out yourself?
Why would I order custom
peach-shaped chocolate for someone else?
Damn.
What do you want for dinner?
Huh?
I know you heard me.
Well, I don’t know yet.
I’m not hungry,
so I can’t think of anything.
Sir.
You really live life with no plans.
That’s who Peachayarat is, huh?
Excuse me?
Pork BBQ, I guess.
See you at 6 p.m. sharp.
My car is parked in front of the company
in the VIP zone.
You saw it before coming in, right?
Wait.
So you came down
to the studio just for this?
Can you not ask anything
that makes me more irritated?
I’m weary.
Our definition of pork BBQ is different.
Do you want anything in particular?
Just pick whatever your heart desires.
Don’t worry about the price.
Aren’t you going to eat?
What are you doing?
I’m sorry.
I was just going to
put some meat on your plate.
You haven’t eaten anything
since we got here.
Your hand.
It’s fine.
I already had your car brought home.
Thank you.
Let’s go to the hospital.
Why?
Your hand got burned.
It’s not that bad.
But you’ve been quiet the whole way here.
I’ve been quiet because
I didn’t want to talk,
not because it hurts.
What’s wrong? Why won’t you talk?
I’m not in a good mood.
Are you angry that I hurt you?
Exactly.
You hadn’t eaten anything,
so I was grilling meat for you.
And what did you do?
You pushed my hand away.
Seriously, did you think
I was going to kill you?
If you don’t trust me this much,
why did you even invite me to dinner?
Peachayarat.
How could I even hurt you?
I’m scared enough that you and your men
came to my house with guns.
Are you scared?
Yes!
I grew up with cameras.
I’m not a mafia boss
who grew up with guns like you.
But I would never use them to shoot you.
Should I be happy or grateful for that?
If your burn stops hurting,
will you stop being angry?
I don’t know. I’ll think about it.
How deep is your anger?
What do I have to do for us
to go back to the way we were?
When you hurt someone, what do you do?
Do you want me to put my hand
on the grill so I’ll hurt like you?
Or do you want a hospital,
a personal doctor, or—
Hey.
That’s not what I mean.
Then what?
(Please, Heaven.)
(Please take all her pain away
and give it to me instead.)
Hey.
Please, Heaven.
Please take all his pain away
and give it to me instead.
Get a grip, Mr. Thee!
(If you come a little closer,)
(you'll hear my heart beating your name.)
What kind of heart beats a person’s name?
Right, Boss?
What’s this sound?
Get a grip, Mr. Thee!
Even people who are closer
wouldn’t do that. It’s weird!
Even a tiny burn on your hand
feels like a wound in my boss’s heart.
When you like someone,
how do you let them know?
(Try to make a good first impression,
like complimenting their outfit.)
That outfit is way too revealing.
Everyone can see it.
Everyone, leave.
What are you guys doing here so late?
I’m sleeping here tonight.
No one can stop me.